https://www.kensar.com/privacy-policy/

Dealer Login
Kensar Equipment Company became a member of the Wolter Group on June 14, 2019.
Wolter Group LLC respects the privacy of its users. Please take a minute to read the following policy so that you can understand how we treat your personal information. As we update and expand our services, this policy might change, so please review it periodically.
This Privacy Policy applies only to this site and not to websites of other companies or organizations to which our site is linked. We are not responsible for the content or the privacy policies of any websites to which this site may link.
This website is the product of Wolter Group LLC. This Privacy Policy is subject to the terms and conditions of our Terms of Use Agreement, including without limitation, the limitations on liability, governing law, and dispute resolution provisions of the Terms of Use Agreement.
What personal information do we collect?
If you are just visiting, you are not required to provide personally identifiable information.
If you are requesting information from Wolter Group LLC web site, you will be asked to provide personal information such as your name, address, email address, etc.
If you are purchasing products or services from Wolter Group LLC, you will be asked to provide personal information such as your name, address, email address, etc.
The information that you enter in the product registration section is collected by one of our third party service providers, and forwarded to Wolter Group LLC.
You may provide us with personally identifiable information in order to allow us to answer a question that you ask us. The information you provide us is transmitted to the appropriate individual on our staff who will contact you directly with a response to your question. Your information may be retained to further improve the products and services we offer you.
Searches: Although we do not currently do so, we may in the future collect and retain information that is entered into the search engines offered on our site.
Cookies: Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. At this time, we use cookies on this site only to recognize whether you are a new or returning visitor to our site. However, we may use cookies in the future to collect demographic information about our visitors, in order to serve them better. This site may, however, include links to third parties who may use cookies. See the Collection of Information By Third Parties section below.
IP Addresses: We compile IP addresses - the location of your computer on the Internet - for administrative and analytical purposes. We do not routinely collect any personally identifiable information through our compilation of your IP address or the location of your computer on the Internet. However, in cases of suspected abuse or service problems, we may use an IP address in conjunction with other personally identifiable information to enforce our terms of service and to protect or troubleshoot the service, the site, its users or others who may be affected. No personally identifiable information associated with IP addresses will be shared with third parties for marketing purposes without your permission.
How do we use the information we collect?
The information you provide us in the product registration section will be used by us for internal market research. In the future, we may send you mail, email and/or newsletters to provide you with information about us and our products.
We do not sell your personally identifiable information to any third parties. We may share your personally identifiable information with third parties in order to allow them to perform analytical and other services for us. For example, we will share your personally identifiable information with our third party service providers to help us manage your information and perform services for you. In some cases, we may also work with third parties that do analysis and development on our behalf. We will share your personally identifiable information with such third parties only on the condition that the third parties maintain the information as confidential and use the information only to perform the services specified by us.
How do we handle changes to your information or to this policy?
Notification of Changes: Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on our web site at this location.
Newsletters and direct promotion: If you would prefer not to receive any direct mailings, emails or newsletters from us, please complete and return to us the "opt-out" reply form that accompanies your mailing.
Security
While we try to maintain integrity of your personal information, none of the information that you transmit through this site is or will be encrypted, and we cannot guarantee that the personally identifiable information which you submit on the site will be secure.
Collection of Information by Third Parties
We allow a variety of third parties to place links on our site. Third-parties who place links on the this site have their own privacy policies regarding their collection and use of your personally identifiable information. To understand the privacy practices of these third parties, please review the privacy policies that are posted on these third party web sites.
Contact Details
If at any time you wish to contact us with any question or complaint or to exercise any of the rights set out in this Privacy Policy, you may do so by either of the methods set out below:
Email Address: contactus@woltergroupllc.com
MENU
Aerial Lifts
Used Aerial Lifts
New Inventory
New Aerial Lift Info
Lift Trucks
Used Lift Trucks
